<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<QuestionForm xmlns="http://mechanicalturk.amazonaws.com/AWSMechanicalTurkDataSchemas/2005-10-01/QuestionForm.xsd">
  <Overview>
    <Title>Write the Next Sentence in the Story</Title>
    <FormattedContent><![CDATA[
      Continue the Ever Turking Story.
      <h2>Overview</h2>
      This is part of a crowd sourcing project to write a story.  Four people will read the latest several sentences of
      the story and write the next sentence.  Seven other people will vote on which of the four sentences is best.
      The winning sentence gets added to the story and the cycle repeats again.
      <p>
      The story should be written as an over-the-top noir mystery with a dry sense of humor.
      <h2>Story Setting</h2>
      The story takes place in a sprawling generic city called Generic City located somewhere in the western USA.
      The time period is current.  It is the month of August.  The story should take place within the span of a
      few weeks at most.  Generic City has a lot of suburbs, malls, small office buildings, small public buildings,
      etc.  It has an central industrial section with old, tall brick buildings which are just starting to be
      gentrified.
      <h2>The Characters</h2>
      <h3>Raspian</h3>
      Raspian is a twenty-something male hipster who looks a bit like a young Rasputin.  He lives semi-legally in
      a loft in one of the industrial buildings that is mostly abandoned along with his girlfriend Hazel.  Rasputin
      is intellectual, outside-the-system, and is clever at building things with available parts.  He works as a
      highly specialized metal worker for a small company that fixes nearly-antique equipment.  Raspian is a
      fearless introvert.
      <h3>Hazel</h3>
      Hazel is an upscale clothing retail worker from Beijing, China.  Short and athletic with perfectly silky
      medium length black hair, guys hit on her constantly.  Hazel works hard to stay current with trends and
      fashions.  It was Hazel's idea to move into the loft; she has ideas and plans.
      <h2>The Situation</h2>
      Raspian returns home late from work to find that someone has left a note on the entrance to his loft saying
      "We have your monkey.  Meet us at the dark end of Danger Street at midnight or the monkey loses his suit and tie."
      This makes no sense because neither Raspian nor Hazel have even seen a monkey outside of a zoo, especially one
      wearing a suit and tie.  The GPS shows danger street in the middle of the old industrial section of Generic City.
      <h2>Your Job</h2>
      Below you will find the latest sentences in the story.  You will write a sentence to continue the story.  You
      should avoid jerking the story around randomly.  You should accept completely whatever the previous sentences
      say, no matter how ridiculous.  Keep in mind that you are competing with four other people who are also writing
      the next sentence.  Seven other Turker workers will vote on which one they like best.
      <p>
      Good luck!
      <h2>Payment Structure</h2>
      You will receive the princely sum of one cent for writing a sentence.  If your sentence is selected in the
      voting, then you will receive an additional 5 cents.
      <h2>Task</h2>
    ]]></FormattedContent>
  </Overview>
  <Question>
    <QuestionIdentifier>writeSentence</QuestionIdentifier>
    <DisplayName>Write the next sentence in the story</DisplayName>
    <QuestionContent>
	<Text>
	</Text>
    </QuestionContent>


    <AnswerSpecification>
      <FreeTextAnswer>
        <Constraints>
            <Length minLength="3" maxLength="128"/>
        </Constraints>
        <NumberOfLinesSuggestion>3</NumberOfLinesSuggestion>
      </FreeTextAnswer>
    </AnswerSpecification>
  </Question>
</QuestionForm>

